Guide to the Rev. William A. Lawson papers, 1955-2008 MS 532
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rev. William A. Lawson papers
1955-2008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Lawson, William A., Rev.
MS 532
8 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
This collection documents the path of Rev. William A. "Bill" Lawson as a minister and religious educator in Houston, Texas. It includes teaching materials, recorded sermons, notes for sermons, and church bulletins for Wheeler Avenue Baptist Church.
Biographical Sketch
Rev. William Alexander Lawson (1929- ), is the founding Pastor of Wheeler Avenue Baptist Church located in Houston, Texas. Established in March 1962 with 13 members, the congregation has grown in excess of 3,500 members. The initial emphasis of the church was to help meet the spiritual needs of Baptists in a transitional community near Texas Southern University, but has become one of the leading Baptist churches in the city of Houston. Early in his career, Rev. Lawson served as Director of the Baptist Student Union and Professor of Bible Studies at Texas Southern University in Houston. He shared in the formation of the first Afro-American Studies Program at the University of Houston, where he taught classes in Sociology and the Black Church. Rev. Lawson is a community leader and social activist. He conceived and organized the United Way's Houston Homeless Initiative in response to the growing number of homeless and jobless persons. More than $4 million was raised in a four-year period in support of that initiative. He established a service agency, the Central City Comprehensive Community Center to serve community needs of citizens in the inner. Rev. Lawson also was instrumental in creating a program to register and mobilize voters in the predominantly African American precincts of the city. In 1996, a group of friends gifted to Rev. Lawson a non-profit organization called the William A. Lawson Institute for Peace and Prosperity ('WALlPP"), to help bridge the gap between the powerful and the powerless. Through this institute, Rev. Lawson brought attention to Olivewood Cemetery, the oldest African American cemetery in the city of Houston, which through many years of neglect had become very overgrown. The attention he brought to Olivewood Cemetery cemetery was the conduit that brought together all the businesses and organizations affected by the METRO rail system traveling down Main Street, eventually to be known as The Main Street Coalition.
Rev. Lawson created the first charter school for boys grades 6 through 8 within the Houston Independent School District called the WALIPP Preparatory Academy. Rev. Lawson is the recipient of the 1991 Silver Beaver Award in support of Scouting. He organized and sponsored the area's largest and most productive scouting program. In its 35-year history, Wheeler Avenue Baptist Church's troops have produced over 100 Eagles.
Rev. Lawson did his undergraduate work at Tennessee Aand I State University, Nashville, Tennessee where he received a Bachelor of Arts Degree, returning to deliver the 1962 Baccalaureate address. He graduated cum laude from Central Baptist Theological Seminary, Kansas City, Kansas where he received the Master of Theology and the Bachelor of Divinity degrees. While there, he majored in New Testament Interpretation and was appointed Teaching Fellow in Homiletics. In 1986 he received an Honorary Doctor of Divinity from Howard Payne University, in Brownwood, Texas; and in 1993, he received an Honorary Doctor of Humane Letters from the University of Houston. Rev. Lawson is married to Audrey H. Lawson, who is associated with The Ensemble Theatre. They have four children; Melanie, Cheryl, Eric and Roxanne, and two grandchildren, Robyn and Raven.
Scope and Contents
This collection reflects the ministerial career of the Rev. William A. Lawson, and comprises eight boxes. Materials include sermons, letters and speeches written by Lawson, as well as photographs, bulletins and audiocassettes.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift donated to Rice University by Rev. Lawson in 2009.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research. Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Index Terms
Subjects
Community activists; African Americans; Religion
Document Types
audiotapes; photographs; lecture notes; speeches; church bulletins; sermons
Places
Texas -- Houston
Subjects (Persons)
Lawson, William A., Rev.; Lawson, Audrey H. (Mrs. William A.)
- Series I: Teaching materials, 1955-2001.
  - NT131-A Survey of the New Testament; Fall, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - OT131-A Survey of the Old Testament; Spring, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - NT132-A Survey of the New Testament; Spring, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - OT131-A Survey of the Old Testament; Spring, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - NT131-The Life of Christ; Fall, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - NT132-Epistles and Revelation; Spring, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - NT131-A Survey of the New Testament; Summer, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - OT131-A Survey of the Old Testament; Fall, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - OT131-A Survey of the New Testament; Spring, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - NT132-Acts, Epistles, and Revelation; Spring, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - OT131-A Survey of the Old Testament; Fall, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - NT131-The Life and Times of Jesus; Fall, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - OT131-A Survey of the Old Testament; Spring, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NT132-A Survey of the New Testament (Acts, Epistles, Revelation); Spring, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - OT131-A Survey of the Old Testament; Fall, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - OT131-A Survey of the Old Testament; Spring, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NT132-New Testament History; Spring, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - TSU-Bible Chair (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Opening the Bible - Non-credit College Survey Course (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Systematic Bible Institute-Epochs of Apostle Paul (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Systematic Bible Institute-The Early Church (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Systematic Bible Institute-Homiletics (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Systematic Bible Institute-Parables (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Systematic Bible Class (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Systematic Ministers Class-Biblical Theology (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bible Class-Interdenominational Theological Center (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Workbook for the New Testament (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Survey of the Bible, Bible Study 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Assorted Teaching Materials (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Series II: Sermons, lectures, publications, c. 1965-2006.
  - Rice U.-Reli 272; Lawson sermon, speech material (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Illustrations and Compiled Information (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Information on 1929 Stock Market Crash (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Prairie View A and M University-Speech to "1000 Man Empowerment March" (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sermon Notes, Informational Material, Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - TSU Commencement Address (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 1 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 2 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 3 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 4 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 5 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 6 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 7 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 8 of 16. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 9 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 10 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 11 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 12 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 13 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 14 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 15 of 16. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Folder 16 of 16 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 1 of 40 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 2of 40. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 3 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 4 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 5 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 6 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 7 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 8 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 9 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 10 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 11 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 12 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 13 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 14 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 15 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 16 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 17 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 18 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 19 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 20 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 21 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 22 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 23 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 24 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 25 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 26 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 27 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 28 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 29 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 30 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 31 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 32 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 33 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 34 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 35 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 36 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 37 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 38 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 39 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 40 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Sermon and Lecture Materials; Envelope 41 of 40. (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Series III: Taped Recordings of Sermons (audiocassettes, one per sermon), 1996-2004
  - January 7, 1996: "Putting God First in "96." (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 14, 1996: "God is in Control." (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 21, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 28, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 4, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 11, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 25, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 3, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 31, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 7, 1996: Easter Sunday. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 14, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 21, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 28, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 5, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 19, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 26, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 23, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 30, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 14, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 28, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 11, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service.
  - August 25, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 1, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 8, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 15, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 29, 1996: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 6, 1996: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 16, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 20, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 4, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 18, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 25, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 8, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 22, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 29, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 13, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 27, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 3, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 10, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 17, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 24, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 7, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 14, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 28, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 5, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 26, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 2, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 16, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 23, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 7, 1997: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 28, 1997: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 4, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 18, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 25, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 1, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 1, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 5, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 12, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 19, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 3, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 17, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 24, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 14, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 28, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 5, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 19, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 26, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 30, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 9, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 13, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 27, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 25, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 8, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 3, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 17, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 24, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 24, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 7, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Servicee. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 7, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 21, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 21, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 28, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 7, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 4, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 4, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 11, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 11, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 25, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 25, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 2, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 2, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 16, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 23, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 30, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 13, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 13, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 20, 1999: "Sunday Nite Live". (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 27, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 11, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 8, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 5, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 12, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 26, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 3, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 17, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 24, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 24, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 31, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 7, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 7, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 14, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 21, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 28, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 5, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 5, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 19, 1999: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 26, 1999: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 2, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 9, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 16, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 23, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 6, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 13, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 20, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 27, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 12, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 19, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 26, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 2, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 16, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 23, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 30, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 7, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 21, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 11, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 25, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 13, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 20, 2000: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 27, 2000: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 6, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 13, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 27, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 3, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 10, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 17, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 24, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 10, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 31, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 14, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 21, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 28, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 5, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 26, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 3, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 17, 1998: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 24, 1998: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 23, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 7, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 14, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 21, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 11, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 18, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 25, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 1, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 8, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 22, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 29, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 6, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - October 20, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 10, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - November 17, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 8, 2002: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - December 15, 2002: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 19, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - January 26, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - February 16, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 2, 2003: "What We Should Learn From Lent". (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 23, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - March 30, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 6, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 13, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - April 20, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - May 25, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 1, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 8, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - June 22, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 6, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 13, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 20, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - July 27, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 3, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 10, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 17, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - August 31, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 7, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 14, 2003: 11:00 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)
  - September 28, 2003: 7:30 a.m. Sunday Service. (Box 4, Folder -)